谢谢你Rado  我们现在已经知道了ListView独特的优势
Thanks, Rado. Now that we know the distinct advantages of using a list view,
我们可以使用ListView在我们的应用中显示天气预报列表
we can use a list view to display the list of weather forecasts in our app.
那现在问题来了  在layout布局文件夹中  我们需要修改那个文件去完成我们的要求呢
Now, which file in the layout folder should we modify to accomplish this?
我们希望在Fragment布局中直接添加一个ListView组件
Well, we want to add the list view directly to the fragment. If you open up
如果你打开fragment_main.xml这个文件  你会注意到这个布局文件
the fragment_main.xml file, you'll notice that the layout includes a relative
已经有了一个RelativeLayout布局作父类布局  当然还有一个TextView组件
layout as the parent view, as well as a child TextView. Modify this file so that
修改这个文件  我们需要替换掉这个TextView组件  换成一个id是listview_forecast的ListView组件
we show a ListView instead of a TextView and assign it an ID ListViewForecast so
以方便我们以后调用它  因为这个布局(RelativeLayout布局)只包含了一个子元素
we can reference it later. Also, since this layout only contains one child's
使用FrameLayout布局实际上会比RelativeLayout布局效率更高
view, it would be more efficient to actually switch to a FrameLayout instead of
当你做完的时候  重新编译  运行你的应用程序
a RelativeLayout. After you make the changes, compile and
你可能会发现一个白白的屏幕空空如也
run your app. You'll be a little underwhelmed with the blank screen, but
但是那是正确的  那是因为我们并没有为这个ListView组建放入任何数据呢
that's okay. That's because we haven't populated the list view with data yet,
放入数据的工作我们随后再讲  做完之后勾选这个复选框噢
and that will come in a later step. Check the box when you're done.